{
    "id": "a35e68f0db764e51ae7ec03da9249791",
    "title": "Although, Though, Despite, and However",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "............................ the watch was expensive, he bought it.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction. We use it before a clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea6a8fde85c3451794bcaa64a0b3fb77"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went out ................................... the rain.",
            "description": "The prepositions 'despite' and 'in spite of' are interchangeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "in spite of",
                "despite",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9234d339b0b4afbb0e19b29a0abb416"
        },
        {
            "question": "We went out ............................... it was raining.",
            "description": "We use 'although' before a clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eb0407823ee943a291f4488dd587139b"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ my husband didn't like the movie, I enjoyed it a lot.",
            "description": "The conjunctions 'though' and 'although' are interchangeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e7edc02e5d24dff84f8851c8bc73cef"
        },
        {
            "question": "He passed the test. ............................, he didn't get the job.",
            "description": "'However' is not a conjunction. It is a transitional adverb and goes at the beginning of the sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44247bf7473b4fbcbc28484935f8bde3"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. he passed the test, he didn't get the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d951507e1a44abca02fe9b90eba9077"
        },
        {
            "question": "They managed to do it ........................... I was not there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "despite",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f652d52b584d4aab9ed50154481044ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tired ............................. he was, he went on working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26dcb3395d624f5b8c2e335a53b3649d"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................... hard she tried, she couldn't do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fafc93e40da94f0fa359df6e340f7adc"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ of the headache, I enjoyed the movie.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'in spite of'. It means the same as 'despite'.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "In spite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7fc3c158e03a4aabb2e758a8717507aa"
        },
        {
            "question": ".......................... I don't agree with him, I think he is honest.",
            "description": "Although is a conjunction. We use it before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50a624a474cc4f0d8c96f5c4611ec442"
        },
        {
            "question": "We understood him ................................ his strong accent.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It goes before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "however",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d86d79303c9140fe933339714e2e6cd3"
        }
    ]
}